Charles W. Thayer Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Charles W. Thayer Archives
1942-1969
IPAR.001139
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
5
The archives of Charles W. Thayer including maps related to his Yale dissertation, "Marine paleoecology of the Upper Devonian Genesee Group of New York."
Thayer, Charles W.
Biographical Sketch
B.A., Dartmouth College, 1966; M. Phil., 1969, Ph.D., 1972, Yale University.
Description of the Material
USGS 7.5" topographic quadrangle maps of New York related to his Yale dissertation, "Marine paleoecology of the Upper Devonian Genesee Group of New York." Also, 2 field notebooks and the locality register from his dissertation.
Connecticut; New York; USA; Maps; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Maps, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Topographic Maps of New York.
  - 1940-1945., 001142
    - Field notes. Schenevus NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002149
    - Field notes. Norwich NY, 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1944; 002142
    - Topographic map. Groton NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1942; 002126
    - Topographic map. Ludlowville NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1942; 002132
    - Topographic map. Sheldrake NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1942; 002150
    - Topographic map. Trumansburg NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1942; 002154
    - Topographic map. Ovid NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1942; 002160
    - Topographic map. Charlotteville NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002118
    - Topographic map. Cincinnatus NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002119
    - Topographic map. Cuyler NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002121
    - Topographic map. Earlville NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002122
    - Topographic map. East Pharsalia NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002123
    - Topographic map. Erieville NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002124
    - Topographic map. Holmesville NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002127
    - Topographic map. Milford NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002135
    - Topographic map. Morris NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002137
    - Topographic map. Mt Vision NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002138
    - Topographic map. New Berlin North NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002139
    - Topographic map. New Berlin South NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002140
    - Topographic map. Norwich NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002141
    - Topographic map. Oneonta NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002143
    - Topographic map. Otselic NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002144
    - Topographic map. Sherburne NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002151
    - Topographic map. South Otselic NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002152
    - Topographic map. West Davenport NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002157
    - Topographic map. West Groton NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002158
    - Topographic map. Pitcher NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1944; 002147
    - Topographic map. Gilboa NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1945; 002125
    - Topographic map. Prattsville NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1945; 002148
    - Topographic map. Stamford NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1945; 002153
  - 1946-1950., 001143
    - Topographic map. Ithaca East NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1949; 002129
    - Topographic map. Ithaca West NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (shaded relief, 1959)., 1949; 002130
    - Topographic map. Ithaca West NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1949; 002131
    - Topographic map. Oxford NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1949; 002146
    - Topographic map. Tyner NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1949; 002155
    - Topographic map. Whitney Point NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1949; 002159
    - Topographic map. Burdett NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1950; 002117
    - Topographic map. Marathon NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1950; 002133
    - Topographic map. Montour Falls NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1950; 002136
    - Topographic map. West Danby NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1950; 002156
  - 1951-1960., 001144
    - Topographic map. Beaver Dams NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1953; 002115
    - Topographic map. Cortland NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1955; 002120
    - Topographic map. Homer NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1955; 002128
    - Topographic map. McGraw NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1955; 002134
    - Topographic map. Owasco NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1955; 002145
    - Topographic map. New York State, Index of Topographic Maps (1: 1000000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1957; 002116
  - 1961-1970., 001145
    - Topographic map. New York State, Index of Topographic Maps (1: 1000000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1967; 002229
    - Topographic map. Ithaca East NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1969; 002163
    - Topographic map. Ithaca West NY, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1969; 002164
- Miscellaneous, Series II
  Miscellaneous archives including Charles W. Thayer's feild notes and dissertation.
  - Dissertation. Charles W. Thayer's dissertation and supporting figures., 001147
    - Locality information. Parts of dissertation with locality and faunal information on Devonian Genesee: New York. 1969, 1970, 000323
  - Field Notes., 001146
    - Field notes. Field Notebooks (2 originals sent to Yale, Feb. 2002), Devonian Genesee: New York. 1968, 1969, 1970, 000534